James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
James F. McNulty Papers 1925-2002
MS 341
McNulty, James F.
Contains political, business, and personal correspondence, newspaper clippings, reports, and photographs.
75 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
With the exception of Subgroup 3, Series 1, there are no access restrictions. Because of the confidential nature of Subgroup 3, Series 1, these records have been closed to researchers until 2028.
Biographical Note
James “Jim” F. McNulty, Jr. has been a resident of Arizona since 1946. He was born in Boston, Massachusetts on October 18, 1925. After graduating from Boston Latin School, he entered the United States Army, and served until the end of WWII. After WWII, McNulty entered the University of Arizona in Tucson, Arizona and attended the University of Arizona College of Law, graduating in 1951. After graduation, he joined the firm of Gentry and Gentry in Bisbee, Arizona.
McNulty married Jacqueline “Jackie” Boevers of Clinton, Arizona in 1950. They are the parents of three children, Michael, Cynthia, and Amy.
McNulty served as city attorney for Bisbee, Tombstone, and Huachuca City. He has been a member of the State Board of Education, the State Hospital Board, the Board of Governors at the state and county level, the Arizona Board of Regents, Catholic Charities, the Board of Visitors for the University of Arizona College of Law, and various volunteer and charitable organizations throughout Southeastern Arizona.
In 1968, McNulty was elected to the Arizona State Senate, where he served until 1975. While a member of the Senate, he won support from Republican leaders as well as his fellow Democrats. During his tenure in the Senate, McNulty was known for his high morals and honesty and enjoyed a reputation as an extremely effective legislator.
McNulty has long been active in the Democratic Party. He has served as County Chairman of Cochise County, Precinct Committee person, delegate to the 1960 Democratic National Convention, Arizona member of the National Democratic Party Platform Committee in 1960, Vice-chairperson of the Arizona Democratic Party, Southern Arizona Coordinator for the Carter/Mondale 1976 Presidential Campaign, and State Co-Chairman of the 1978 Babbitt for Governor Campaign Committee.
McNulty ran for the House of Representatives in 1976 but dropped out of the race when Morris Udall was defeated in his run for the White House and decided to retain his seat in the House. McNulty ran for the U.S. Senate in 1980 and was defeated. McNulty was successful in running for the House of Representatives in 1982, but was defeated in his re-election bid by Jim Kolbe. After his term in the House of Representatives, McNulty retired to private practice in Tucson, Arizona.
McNulty returned to Tucson in January, 1985 and became a partner with the firm of Bilby and Shoenhair which was merged into the firm of Snell and Wilmer in May, 1989. He was a senior partner in each firm. He served briefly in Guatemala with the Peace Corps. After the Peace Corps, he practiced law with the firm of brown and Bain in Tucson. He served as a member of the Board of Governors of the State Bar Board of Governors and was a member of the Arizona Bar Foundation, the American Bar Association, and the Pima County Bar Association. He passed away on June 30, 2009.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight subgroups:
Subgroup I: Political Activity, 1957-1985
Subgroup II: Volunteer Activity, 1958-1983
Subgroup III: Legal/Business 1929-2002
Subgroup IV: Personal/Family 1935-1995
Subgroup V: Photographs 1953-1987
Subgroup VI: Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks 1930's-1990's
Subgroup VII: Travel Slides no date
Subgroup VIII: Ephemera 1949-1995
Subgroup IX: Audiovisual Material 1976-1984
Scope and Content Note
This collection documents the activities of James F. McNulty, who was a member of the Arizona State Senate from 1968 till 1975, and a member of The United States House of Representatives from 1982 to 1984. The political papers housed in this collection include materials from 1957-1985, such as McNulty’s various activities within the Democratic Party, which include correspondences, reports, minutes, pamphlets from the 1960 DNC and material associated with a 1962 national delegation to the USSR. The collection also comprises a wealth of documentation concerning McNulty’s various volunteering activities, his involvement in 4-H, Arizona Board of Regents, Arizona State Bar Association, Arizona State Board of Education, Catholic Church, the Cochise County Hospital Association and the Copper Queen Hospital Association, Health Systems Agency of Southern Arizona, Arizona State Hospital, the League of Arizona Cities and Towns, the University of Arizona College of Law. It also includes personal materials, including the records of McNulty’s business (his legal files are closed until 2028), files relating to Cochise Junior College and DSET, personal and family material from 1953 to 1986. The “Photographs” subgroup contains official and unofficial photographs and postcards documenting McNulty’s 1962 visit to the USSR, a collection of photographs taken during McNulty’s time in the House of Representatives, and miscellaneous photos of McNulty in the military, at the University of Arizona, throughout his state political career. Also included are several collections of newspaper clippings and scrapbooks from 1943 to 1997, one collection specifically documenting McNulty’s stint in the U. S. House of Representatives, and another documenting the 1982 campaign for the House of Representatives. Also included are slides from various travels to Russia, Canada and the Southwest. Finally, there is a grouping of certificates and memorabilia reflecting McNulty’s dedication to his profession, politics, the University of Arizona and the state of Arizona.
Babbitt, Bruce E.; Carter, Jimmy, 1924-; Mondale, Walter F., 1928-; Udall, Morris K.; Kolbe, Jim, 1942-; Udall, Stewart L.; Frost, Robert, 1874-1963; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963; Political campaigns; Political candidates; Politics and governments of the American states; United States Politics and government 1945-1989; City attorneys; United States. Congress. House; Arizona; Tucson (Ariz.); Bisbee (Ariz.); Tombstone (Ariz.); Huachuca City (Ariz.); Cochise County (Ariz.); Photographs; Slides; Pamphlets
Container List
- Subgroup 1: Political Activity, 1957 – 1985
  "Political Activity," contains political material from 1957-1985. Series One consists of McNulty’s Democratic Party activities, which includes correspondence, reports, minutes, as well as pamphlets from the 1960 Democratic National Convention and McNulty’s trip to the USSR in 1962 as part of a national delegation with Secretary of the Interior Stewart Udall. Series Two contains material from the Arizona State Senate, and includes correspondence, reports, voting records, and his work on the Commission on salaries for elective state officers during the 33rd legislature (1977-1978). Series Three consists of material from his various campaigns. Series Four consists of material collected while serving in the U.S. House of Representatives (1982-1984). This series contains, correspondence, and reports. Photographs and newspaper clippings for these corresponding years can be found in subgroup five and six.
  - Series 1: Arizona Democratic Party Activities, 1957 – 1980
    - Democratic Party—Bruce Babbitt for Attorney General, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Bruce Babbitt—Governor, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1957-October 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, May 1959-October 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, November 1959-December 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, February 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, March 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, April 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, May 1960-June 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, July 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, August 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, September 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, October 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, November 1960-December 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1960-May 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, June 1961-November 1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1962-April 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, May 1962-June 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, July 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, August 1962-September 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, October 1962-December 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1963-June 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, July 1963-August 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, September 1963-December 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, February 1964-May 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, June 1964-July 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, August 1964-September 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, October 1964-November 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, March 1965-December 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, February 1967-December 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1968-February 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, March 1968-April 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, May 1968-June 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, July 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, August 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, September 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, October 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, November 1968-December 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, January 1969-March 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, June 1969-October 1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, June 1971-August 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, October 1976-June 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence, No Date (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Correspondence—Cards and Invitations, December 1958-February 1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Party—Characture, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee, September 1954-November 1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee, September 1958-April 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee—Finances, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee—Members, September 1975-May 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee—Minutes, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee—Notes, No Date (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Cochise County Democratic Committee—Proxy slips, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Concerned Citizens for Total Representation—stationary, No Date (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Correspondence, July-August 17, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Correspondence, August 22, 1962-November 19, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Correspondence, November 28, 1962-July 5, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Books, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Books, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Journal, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Pamphlets, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Pamphlets, maps, etc, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Postcards, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Delegation to the USSR—Postcards, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Committee—Fact sheets, March 1960-January 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Convention, June-July 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Convention—Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Convention—Invitations, tickets, pamphlets, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Convention—Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic National Convention—Jimmy Carter for President, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic State Central Committee, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—Democratic Telethon, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—Department of Interior—Speech, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—Elections, 1956-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—Ephemera, No Date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Gubernatorial Campaign—Re-elect Sam Goddard—Committee Reports, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Gubernatorial Campaign—Re-elect Sam Goddard—Correspondence, August-November 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Gubernatorial Campaign—DeConcini for Governor, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Lyndon Johnson—Inaugural Address, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Lyndon Johnson—State of the Union Address, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Maps—Warren, No Date (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Morris Udall, No Date (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Party—Morris Udall for President—Delegates, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party—National campaign manuals, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party—National campaign—Pamphlets, newspaper clippings, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party—National campaign—Promotional material, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party—National campaign—Carter/Mondale—Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party—National campaign—Carter/Mondale, Southern Arizona Steering Committee, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Party—National Citizens Commission on International Cooperation, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party—Newspaper clippings, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party—Northern Cochise County—Correspondence, No Date (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Party—Northern Cochise County—Notes, No Date (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party—Northern Cochise County—Reports, No Date (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Party—Northern Cochise County—Reports, No Date (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Party—Personal information—Candidates, No Date (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party—Photographs, No Date (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party—Prepared speeches, 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Democratic Party—Primary, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Party—Sandra Day O’Connor—Nomination, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Democratic Party—Speeches, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Democratic Party—Speeches—Robert S. Woods, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Democratic Party—USSR trip, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Series 2: Arizona State Legislature, 1968 – 1976
    - Arizona State Senate—28th legislature (II), 1967-1968—Correspondence, December 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—28th legislature (II), 1967-1968—Correspondence, January 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, April 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, June 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, July 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, August 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate—29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, October 1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, November 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (I), 1969-1970—Correspondence, December 1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, February 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, April 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, May 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, June 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, July 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, August 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, September 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Arizona State Senate--29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Bills for Introduction, September 1969-January 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Arizona State Senate—29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, October 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, November 1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—29th legislature (II), 1969-1970—Correspondence, December 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, January 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, February 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, March 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, April 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, May 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, June 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, July 1-14, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, July 15-27, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, July 28-30, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, August 3-20, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Arizona State Senate--30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, August 21-30, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, September 2-14, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, September 15-28, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, October 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, November 3-12, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, November 13-30, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, December 1-12, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (I), 1971-1972—Correspondence, December 13-31, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, January 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, February 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, May 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, June 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, July 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, August 1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, September 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, October 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, November 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, December 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Arizona State Senate—30th legislature (II), 1971-1972—Correspondence, January 1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, July 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, August 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, September 4-18, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, September 19-28, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, October 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, November 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Correspondence, December 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, January 1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, February 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, March 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, April 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, May 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, June 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, July 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, August 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, September 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)